Please let me take it out.
抜かせてください
I said it twice.
2回言っちゃったけど
Hmm, that's difficult.
う ーん、難しい
said it once
1回言いた
stomach.
い
Ah, it feels good.
あー 気持ちいい
Spit on it.
ツバ垂らして
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
Shadow, I'll do it like this.
影をね、こうするから
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Ah, well done.
あー、上手上手
Ah, it feels good.
あー気持ちいい
Isn't it interesting?
面白くない?
oh
お
- Oh no.
ー やばい
Ah, it feels good.
あー気持ちいい
Wow, I'm about to throw my face.
うわー顔投げそう
hard?
硬い?
hard.
硬い
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
terrible.
やばい
Is this your first time?
こんなの初めて?
You can do it with both hands.
両手でできる
With both hands?
両手で?
how?
どうやって?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Ah, I think I'm going.
あー、行きそう
Shall we go?
行くよ?
Look, look.
見て、見てて
Look at me.
見てて
I was surprised.
びっくりした
A lot came out.
あーいっぱい出た
I was taking it.
取ってた
thank you.
ありがとう
bye bye.
バイバイ